<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jinying Cheng</title>
    <link>https://example.com/docs/EXPERIENMENT/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jinying Cheng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/docs/EXPERIENMENT/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/EXPERIENMENT/B_2108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/EXPERIENMENT/B_2108/</guid>
      <description>Breezy - A pneumatic experiment Breezy is a product designed to help people with scars to care for their neck health and ear health.
“Scar” is always associated closly with illness, tor- ture, shame, and the past. And it will gradually become a symbolic long-term existence as time goes by, which also bring people with sad and unbearable memories. People, es- pecially young women who are left with scars often become unconfident and low self-esteem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/EXPERIENMENT/ST_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/EXPERIENMENT/ST_21/</guid>
      <description>Soft Touch - A collaborative musical instrument concept This small conceptual project was completed during DigitalFutures workshop &amp;ndash; Soft Touch, instructed by professor Sofia Guridi and Emmi Pouta from Aalto University in Finland. The workshop aimed at combining electronic components with flexible textile materials to obtain some further product solutions or concepts.
North pole is shifting. According to researchers, due to the severe climate change, the pole has been moving steadily eastward by about 75 degrees, heading toward the Prime Meridian that runs through Greenwich, England.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>